<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Luca&#39;s Trove</title>
    <link>http://luca-spopo.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Luca&#39;s Trove</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2017 06:38:01 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://luca-spopo.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial</title>
      <link>http://luca-spopo.github.io/tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2017 06:38:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://luca-spopo.github.io/tutorial/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This section is under construction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog</title>
      <link>http://luca-spopo.github.io/blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2017 06:37:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://luca-spopo.github.io/blog/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This section is under construction&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portfolio</title>
      <link>http://luca-spopo.github.io/portfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2017 06:17:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://luca-spopo.github.io/portfolio/</guid>
      <description>specs
   Name Anirudh Katoch     Mugshot Bonus trivia: I wear glasses.   Education Schooling at The Heritage School, New Delhi Currently attending college at Manipal Institute of Technology.  Currently in the 5th semester, perusing a major in Information Technology   Areas of Interest Game development, Research, Anything Interesting&amp;trade;.   Technical Activities Procedural level and art generation (JavaScript, WebGL)
Summer 2016 Developed non-deterministic Cellular Automata, L-systems and Perlin Noise for level generation in video games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pay</title>
      <link>http://luca-spopo.github.io/pay/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2017 06:06:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://luca-spopo.github.io/pay/</guid>
      <description>Hey, thanks for opening this page. I don&amp;rsquo;t really need money for anything right now, and I can&amp;rsquo;t imagine why you would want to send me any. Regardless, my digital wallet codes and paypal link are provided here. I&amp;rsquo;m never going to refuse free things :3
PayPal: spopo
BTC: 1EgmjpJUxuYfZjRkVfXxsC82apibe4zJHW
Ether: 0xcf7bb415f304cc8a72fe44526a03d7a109cec8ab
LiteCoin: LYuj12cK3ZnipY7ufoXG9DBno35skmytcs
Monero: 43XEgHK95EeAeWScgMnELAEEzyt9eyezfd3UD5TDMfabafxyzqpWSRFGmmL1mZnVGeD1tkWhYxPwc6mvq3QSKjXPHLdacAr</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>http://luca-spopo.github.io/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 22:24:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://luca-spopo.github.io/</guid>
      <description>$luca@BOB&amp;gt; pwd 
You have reached the website of Anirudh Katoch. What are you looking for?
If you&amp;rsquo;re a potential employer, then you&amp;rsquo;re probably looking for my portfolio or projects. Please also check out the &amp;ldquo;About me&amp;rdquo; section.
If you&amp;rsquo;re just here to read cool stuff, then check out my projects and my blogs.
If you&amp;rsquo;re here for something else, click one of the menu items on top (The top left button if you&amp;rsquo;re on mobile).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://luca-spopo.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 21:38:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://luca-spopo.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>$luca@BOB&amp;gt; whoami luca 
About me I&amp;rsquo;m Anirudh Katoch, an undergraduate student at Manipal Institute of Technology, Manipal. Currently pursuing a B.Tech in Information Technology. I have a passion for creating things and solving problems (in equal parts). I have found that I am best suited for creating through technology. This is my personal website. Some people prefer to call me Luca, which is my online handle.
 Hobbies?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ash</title>
      <link>http://luca-spopo.github.io/project/ash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://luca-spopo.github.io/project/ash/</guid>
      <description>Ash is a framework/library for MTA that gives you the most flexible and most beautiful UI. Ash does not only provide a beautiful GUI, it also aims to wrap over all other UI. For now that includes GUI, keyboard input and mouse input.
The Problem Multitheft Auto is an open source modification of Rockstar&amp;rsquo;s very successful (and old) game Grand Theft Auto: San Andreas. It adds support for multiplayer (GTA:SA is originally single player only), and lets the server hosting the game change every aspect of the game at run time through Lua scripts that interact with hooks provided by the engine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hewlett Packard Enterprise</title>
      <link>http://luca-spopo.github.io/project/hpe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://luca-spopo.github.io/project/hpe/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My summer internship at HP resulted in the creation of a clever and simple system to tackle a complex problem (Under construction)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Procedural Generation</title>
      <link>http://luca-spopo.github.io/project/proc-play/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://luca-spopo.github.io/project/proc-play/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Procedural level and art generation for tiled video games using noise, upscaling, L-systems and cellular automata.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bakaGaijin</title>
      <link>http://luca-spopo.github.io/project/bakagaijin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://luca-spopo.github.io/project/bakagaijin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;bakaGaijin is an &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Luca-spopo/bakaGaijin/tree/master/bakaGaijin&#34;&gt;open source&lt;/a&gt; (MIT License) project that emerged from the (larger and closed source) &lt;a href=&#34;http://luca-spopo.github.io/project/ash&#34;&gt;Ash&lt;/a&gt; project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It aims to provide seamless cross resource communication across Lua virtual machines in MTA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOSSEE</title>
      <link>http://luca-spopo.github.io/project/fossee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://luca-spopo.github.io/project/fossee/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I had the wonderful opportunity to intern at IIT Bombay to help develop the Image Processing Toolbox for Scilab, a free software developed by French company Scilab Enterprises. I got this opportunity as a member of FOSSEE (Free Open Source Software For Education), an initiative by IIT Bombay to make available open source equivalents of proprietary academic software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>